creative-home.com 2018-08-27

# Creative Co-Op Home

Keeping your personal information secure and ensuring your understanding of how we use that information is important to us. Our goal is to help you understand how the personal information you choose to share with us through the Creative Co-Op Home website is collected, used, and maintained. You may review this Creative Co-Op Home Online Policy Statement at any time by clicking on the Privacy Policy link appearing on the bottom of one or more pages of this website.

**Guests and Registered Users**

You can visit this website to read about our company, its products and services, or other features, all without giving us any personal information about yourself. We may collect anonymous, aggregate information about how you access our website, such as IP address, referring website, domain name, time spent on the website, or web pages visited.

**Categories of Information Collected**

Registration Information: Some of the features on the website require registration before you can use them. If you register to use the website, you choose to provide us with certain personal information such as your name, address, email address, and telephone number. You can update registration information online. You may change your password at any time. Service and Transaction Information: When you use a password or a similar identifier to access the website, we will recognize your identifier and may collect various categories of information about you such as information you give us, data related to your use of the website and its services, and information about your transactions, interactions, and communications with us.

**Use of Collected Information**

We do not sell or market your personal information or personalized data to other organizations. The personal information you provide and the personalized data you create and save on the website is used to provide better service to you and to inform you of products, services, or other opportunities that may be available. This may include disclosure of such information to employees, representatives, officers, agents, affiliates, government and regulatory entities, third parties, and service providers. Such information and data will also be used to administer our business, the website, and our services in a manner consistent with this privacy statement. If you provide us with your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address, or have done so in the past, Creative Co-Op Home may contact you by telephone, mail, or email.

**Aggregate Information**

If you anonymously visit or browse the website without registering or logging on with a username, password, or other registration code, we do not collect your personal information unless you disclose it to us (e.g., email address). We may collect aggregate, technical information that tracks site use including browser type, IP address, domain name, number or type of pages visited, and time spent on the website. We may use such information in a variety of ways, including analyzing trends, visitor interests, or to improve the website.

**Payment**

Creative Co-Op Home and this website do not capture or store your credit card data. Credit card data is encrypted through a third-party merchant, following the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) and never shared with Creative Co-Op Home. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.

**Other Sites and Services**

This website may contain links to other Internet sites not under our direction or control. This privacy statement does not apply to those sites. We are not responsible for such sites, cannot control how such sites use personal information, cookies, or other data, and their representations do not apply to this website. You should always review the privacy representations of those sites that you link to before you use them, and particularly before you share personal information.

**Security**

Creative Co-Op Home maintains your personal information and data according to strict standards of security and confidentiality. Online access to your information is only possible through a secure (SSL capable) web browser. SSL-capable web browsers support encryption technology, which helps prevent unauthorized users from viewing your account information as it travels over the Internet.

**Changes**

Creative Co-Op Home may change this privacy statement at any time. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this website.
